... 34 , 35 , 36 , 37 , 38 , 39 , 40 , 41 , 42 ,
43 , 44 , 45 , 46 , 47 , 48 , 49 , 50 .
- Killer is coming . - The killer is coming .
Killer is coming . Watch out , Kelly .
I hear you .
Hey , Nick ! Missed you .
Here , killer 's here .
Killers are coming , killers are coming .
Killers are coming .
Killers are coming . Killers are coming .
Kill ! Kill ! Kill !
Wendy , you 're it .
All right , but I 'll kill you all .
1 , 2 , 3 , 4 , 5 , 6 , 7 , 8 ...
- Hey , this way . - 18 , 19 , 20 ...
25 , 26 , 27 , 28 , 29 , 30 ...
The killer is coming . The killer 's gonna get you .
L-look , Kim .
It 's Nick .
Nick !
He 's an idiot .
Where 's my geography book ? Darn .
I 've got to go back for it . Robin , you and Alex go on .
Come on .
Come on , they don 't want you in their game .
Well , I 'm not waiting .
A-Alex ... ?
Kill ! Killer 's got you .
There !
The killer 's gonna get you , Kelly .
Shut up .
Killer 's got you , Kelly .
- Now you 've done it . - We know you 're up here , Nick .
The killers are coming .
Here , killers , here .
P-p-please .
Kill . Kill . Kill . Kill .
Kill ! Kill ! Kill !
Killers are coming .
Killers are coming . Killers are coming .
killers are coming .
Killers are coming ...
Kill . Kill . Kill . Kill .
Kill . Kill .
Kill . Kill !
Kill . Kill . Kill . Kill .
Kill ! Kill !
P-p-please .
I d-d-didn 't want to p-play .
Kill ! Kill !
Kill , kill !
Kill . Kill ... !
Kill ! Kill !
Kill , kill !
Kill , kill ...
Kill ! Kill !
We 've got to get somebody , quick .
Are you crazy ? They 'll put us in jail .
If we tell anyone they 'll say it 's our fault .
Who 'd believe it was an accident ?
- But what if ... - Listen to me .
We 'll go home now and never , ever tell anyone .
No one but us will ever know .
- Jude , swear ? - I swear .
- Kelly ? Kelly ! - I don 't want to go to jail .
Swear ?
I swear .
- Nick ? Nick ! - I 'll never tell .
Good . Let 's go .
Probably the victim of a sexual attack .
She must have resisted .
We think we know who 's responsible .
We 'll pick them up for questioning .
Vi . No !
No . No ...
Oh , no .
Uh , Vi ... ?
Time to go . We 've got to get back .
Oh , Vi .
Come on , now , trust me .
Have a date for the prom yet ?
Mm-mm .
Hm , I happen to know Jude 's still available .
Now she is older and very sophisticated .
Come on , Kimbo .
I may be hard up ...
Alex , she 's cute .
Besides , she 's very funny and very intelligent .
It 'll give you somebody to do your equations with .
Oh , great . You know I 'm in charge of the sound system tonight .
Not bad , but it isn 't romance .
- Morning , Mr. Sykes . - He 's wacko .
- Alex , no man is wacko . - He really scares me .
He 's always looking at women . I don 't know .
Kelly says he spies on the girls in the locker room too .
No , Sykes is not a Peeping Tom .
He may have been here for just a short time
but he 's been checked out .
Hello ?
- Jude . - Yes ?
Can you come out to play tonight ?
I 'll see you at the prom .
Still no date ?
- Getting closer though . - A boy ?
An obscene call and not very obscene at that .
Sorry , Mom , gotta run .
- Hey , beautiful , need a lift ? - No thanks .
- Come on , I won 't bite . - So who are you ?
Seymour Crane . But , uh ... they
they call me Slick .
I can see why .
- How old are you , Slick ? - Old enough .
Well , I 've heard about guys like you running over girls on the sidewalk .
For some girls , if they 're ...
if they 're good looking , I give ' em a ride .
I 'm going straight to Hamilton High .
Straight to Hamilton High .
James ' residence .
Kelly .
It 's been a long time .
Tonight ... it 's my turn .
Drew ?
Drew , is that you ?
Kelly .
Where did you come from ?
The back door was open .
I 'm glad to see you too .
Oh , Drew , this horrible voice on the telephone .
- It sounded so ... - What did you get ? A heavy breather ?
It was worse than that .
He turned you on , didn 't he ? Maybe I should try that .
I 'm serious .
So am I.
Come on .
- Come on , Nicky . - Yeah , Dad . I 'm coming .
For a guy so fast on the disco floor , you are the slowest .
It 's okay , Dad , it 's my phone .
- Why didn 't you answer it ? - It 's just Wendy .
She 's mad . She wants me to take her to the prom tonight .
I thought you two broke up .
You can 't tell Wendy anything she doesn 't want to hear .
Are you still going with the Hammond girl , the principal 's daughter ?
Kim .
God , I wish I had your women problems .
Dr. Fairchild , we only wanted him for routine questioning
but he tried to outrun the detectives .
Why did they have to chase him ?
The circumstances of the Hammond girl 's death are unclear .
Murch lived near the place where she died and he 's a known sex offender .
He was . Was , past tense .
It might have helped if your men had stopped harassing him .
Maybe , Dr. Fairchild .
But I believe he killed Robin Hammond .
You wanted to see me ?
Thanks for coming over , Doc . Been a long time .
I 'm on a tight schedule . I hope this is an emergency , Sergeant .
Lieutenant . I was promoted last year .
Great , congratulations . What 's the problem ?
Leonard Murch .
This came over the wire .
Last night , Murch escaped from the state hospital in Cleveland .
He took a nurse and her car with him .
The authorities in Cleveland say he 's violent .
Whew ...
I don 't see how I can help .
I haven 't even seen Leonard since he was institutionalized .
- But you know him . - Knew him , knew him . Past tense .
- You think he 'd head back here ? - I don 't know .
Come on . Even a guess will help .
Lieutenant , you 're asking me to comment on a catatonic schizophrenic
who was disfigured and institutionalized six years ago .
I 'm sorry , I ...
Leonard Murch is an unknown quantity now .
McBride .
Lieutenant , Unit 3 has found that nurse .
- Are they sure ? - Yeah , the description fits .
- Where ? - Down at the old cottonwood .
Okay , I 'll be right over .
He 's back .
Nick ?
Wendy .
Do you still like to play games ?
Oh , get lost , Lou .
Be home for dinner , Wendy ?
How the hell should I know ?
Save it .
- Hi , guys . - Hi , Jude .
- Missed you on the bus today . - I didn 't ride it .
- No kidding . - I got a ride .
- Who with ? - None of your business .
- Who with ? - A guy .
A guy , huh ? Who with , Jude ?
- Who ? - I 'm going to the prom .
What ? What ?
The prom !
Now I know why Kim won 't go out with me .
She likes girls .
It 's better than kissing an ashtray .
- Say goodbye , Lou . - Goodbye , Lou .
Hey , listen , you guys ever get tired of each other ,
I 'm always around , lonely .
Oh really , give us a break .
Good girl , must be exhausting .
Why , look how he has to hold her up .
Go sit on it , ape .
Uh-oh .
- When ? I never . - Yes , you did .
Hi , Nick .
See you later , lover .
- I told her it was over . - Worked real well .
Kim ... ?
- That 's cruel . - Oh , no , you don 't .
Nick , she 's smiling .
Got a big grin spread all over her face .
Race ya , honey blonde .
No ! Women in love coming through .
- Where 's the medical examiner ? - He 's on his way .
I also called for the meat wagon .
Any sign of her car ?
No , Murch must have driven it off after killing her .
I got an APB out on it .
Shouldn 't be too hard to find a beat-up VW .
Hey , don 't touch that .
Might be the murder weapon .
Can I take a look at the girl ?
Some butcher job , huh ?
Well , now we know he 's back in town .
Next question is why ?
Your guess is as good as mine , Lieutenant .
Revenge ?
Against who ?
You . The police .
- The whole town . - Oh , great .
All we need is a full-scale panic on our hands .
Lieutenant , I think it would be wiser
to keep quiet about this for now .
Come on , you mean not tell ' em
that there 's a homicidal fruitcake on the loose ?
Now think about it .
Leonard can 't move around freely , not the way he looks .
Yeah , you got a point .
And we don 't even know if he 's still in town .
I fail to see any good
in needlessly terrifying the entire community .
Listen , the last thing I want to do is ...
Then keep it quiet .
If it is Leonard ,
we should be able to pick him up before nightfall .
I hope you 're right .
Bravo .
Practicing for tonight ?
As a matter of fact , I was .
Practice makes perfect . Kim is always so perfect .
Uh , Nick likes me that way .
Really ?
You are keeping in mind that after tonight is all over ,
everything 's gonna be back to normal ?
I mean , Nick is King of the Prom
and you just happen to be Queen of the Prom .
But that 's as far as it goes , Hammond .
You really ought to tell him that .
I 'm telling you , okay ?
You seem a little anxious , Wendy .
By the way , who are you going with tonight ?
It 's not who you go with , honey .
It 's who takes you home .
I 'll try and remember .
You wait and see . Just wait and see .
I can 't believe they got it ready on time .
Yeah , that disco floor looked fantastic .
- Know how much it cost ? - How much ?
Don 't ask .
Here 's the incredible hunk himself .
Mm-hm , looks like a party .
Yeah , I don 't think he 's gonna be too good for my diet .
Mm-hm .
Thank you . What else ?
- How about a muffin ? - No , cookie ...
Like me better now ?
It 's an improvement .
Well , if you like it so much , why don 't you taste ?
- No ... - Come on , be nice .
No , let go !
Alex !
Get off of him !
Get off !
Get off of him ! Alex !
Alex !
No , no !
Alex ?
Cool it . Cool it !
That 's it , Perano , this time you 're out .
Look , man , he started it .
Alex ?
He was just trying to help me .
You better come along with us to your father 's office .
Are you okay ?
It just didn 't work out , Wendy . Why can 't we just leave it at that ?
Well , because I don 't want to leave it at that .
I do .
Well , you blew it .
Lou ?
I got this appointment .
I 'll wait .
Vi , I have to go now .
Now , we will be there within the hour .
Well , if you ...
Hello ?
You again ?
Brawling in the cafeteria , both of them .
All right , thank you . I 'll handle this .
Explanations .
Look , I was just fooling around with this girl .
Kim .
And this ... your son , he belted me .
Is that true , Alex ?
- Huh , I knew it . - You knew what ?
- Well , it just figures . - That I 'd play favorites ?
I 'd take it easy on Alex because he 's my son ? Well , you 're right .
You have been nothing but a disgrace to this school and this community .
You 're suspended indefinitely . Now get out .
I 'll see you around .
Go and have the nurse take a look at you .
And come on back .
The same place he killed Robin Hammond .
Why back here ?
What 's he trying to prove ?
Revenge .
Against who ?
Psychotic ...
disfigured ...
violent .
He has to be hiding somewhere .
Waiting .
I 've got to get that bastard before he butchers someone else .
You don 't seem very excited .
I am . It 's just ...
in some ways , it 's such an awful day .
It 's Robin 's day .
My mom 's all upset .
Dad is too . He 's just too strong to show it .
You know , she would have been a junior this year ?
Would have been her first prom .
But the Queen of the Prom must maintain her
whatever .
I love you .
You know that ?
I love you too .
I want you to know , Robin 's death , I remember it .
I 've always been really sorry about it .
I mean , I know what you 're feeling .
I ...
Listen , Kim ...
I , uh ...
I got to go .
Yeah .
See you later .
- It 's a nice car . - Gets me around .
Thank you .
- You ready to order ? - Yes . What would you like ?
- Well , I 'm a little short of cash . - You can owe me .
Yeah ? Oh , well , I 'll have a couple of burgers ,
large fries and , uh , what kind of beer you got ?
Come on , man , this is a drive-in , not a bar .
All right , don 't get nervous .
Just bring me a Coke and bring her the same .
No , a small diet cola , please .
That 's it ?
Yes , that 's it .
Nice .
I 'll buy you one for Christmas , all right ?
Lou ... ?
Lou !
How do I know you 're serious about this ?
What do you mean , serious ?
Man , I hate that school , Hammond and his whole fucking family .
Okay , okay .
Listen , I don 't want anyone hurt .
Not badly .
I 'll take care of it . Don 't worry about it .
You 'll be in the gym promptly at 3 : 15 for rehearsal , Kim ?
All right , girls , let 's try this again .
Mr. Sykes ... ?
This is just for you .
Vicki ?
Vicki ! Come here this instant .
And you too , Jude .
I 'm not like the others , Kim .
Drew needs somebody like Vicki who 'll give him what he wants .
Vicki 's sex life is more talk than action .
Besides , Drew wants you .
I dunno . If I don 't do it with him ,
I know he 'll find somebody who will .
- So ? Let him . - I 'd die if he did .
- What about you and Nick ? - What about me and Nick ?
What happened when he asked you ?
Maybe I asked him .
Come on . Come on , Wendy . I 've got a thousand things to do .
So ? You think I don 't ?
What 's this ? Is this supposed to be funny ?
- I didn 't do it . - No .
You 're all idiots .
- I didn 't . - Oh , shut up !
She 's out of her mind .
I think I 'll let Drew do it .
Let him ? Oh , that 'd be interesting .
Oh , you know what I mean .
Well , I can 't believe it .
Hello ?
Who did it ? Did you see ?
Uh-uh .
Who was here ?
I don 't know .
Let 's find out . Come on .
Come on .
- Who would do that ? - I don 't know . Why ?
- Kelly ... ? - What ?
Careful , Monty . A little higher .
- Sorry I 'm late . - Oh , I 'm glad you could make it .
Yeah . If it isn 't the literary Miss Hammond .
Let 's get started .
Alex !
All set , Miss Ransom . Just updating all the tapes .
Oh , wonderful .
You can be Mr. Hammond for the rehearsal .
Nick and Kim , onstage .
George , could you close the curtains , please ?
Now , you 'll wait here .
Nick ? Nick ?
Scary place .
Look , you are gonna be standing up here tonight and not me .
And if you don 't know what to do , you 'll look the fool .
Come on .
Over there .
Can you both hear me ?
Yes .
- Can you hear me , Kim ? - Mm-hm .
All right , Davy , start the tape .
King and Queen of the Alexander Hamilton
High School Junior Senior Prom for 1980 ,
Nick McBride and Kim Hammond .
These two seniors were selected by their fellow students
as the most popular boy and girl in the class .
Bull .
Nick is a three-sport letterman
and president of the Key Club .
He plans to attend State University in the fall .
' Cause he couldn 't get in anywhere else .
Kim is the head of the Dance Club
and an all-around athlete ranked number one on the girls ' tennis team .
- She hopes to become a teacher . - If she ever graduates .
Now , Alex .
That 's it , Alex . Now kiss her .
- It 's my sister . - Alex .
Good . Now the king .
- Kiss the king ? - On the mouth .
Shake hands .
Now step back , Alex .
All right , Kim and Nick , move to the center of the floor .
Now wait for your spotlights and your music cue .
And dance .
It 'll be beautiful .
Jude , look .
Why ?
Yeah , we 've done that , Lieutenant .
We got checkpoints at all the main roads
and the other units are covering all the streets ,
plazas and garages around here .
If that blue VW is still in town , we 'll find it .
One more thing , Sayer ,
I want you to make sure to double check the whole ...
the whole area around the high school , okay ?
- Will do , Lieutenant . - See you later .
Hm , what am I wearing now ?
Oh , tonight ?
Yeah , well , you 'll see soon enough .
- Yeah , I guess . - Okay , now listen , is it all set ?
It better . I don 't want her ever to forget this night .
- Don 't worry about it , Wendy . - Okay .
Bye , bye .
- Kim ? - Yeah ?
Do you remember that dark red lipstick that you like ?
- Did you take it ? - No . I haven 't seen it .
Why does everything have to happen at the last minute ?
Mom ? Mom ? You look terrific .
I remember putting it on the dressing table .
I saw it on the dressing table , I know it was there .
I 'm sure you did .
You look lovely , dear .
Thank you .
Well ?
- Amazing . - You like ?
You look almost like a woman .
Oh , thank you .
You 're welcome .
Are you gonna help me with these or are you gonna just stand there and leer ?
You 're my sister . I 'll leer .
You 're gonna get over here .
Thank you .
Oh , you 've done this before , I see .
- Stop it . - No .
Now .
Stop it ! I smell like the ladies ' room .
How would you know ? Oh , of course , you know everything .
- He 's here . - Better hurry .
Would you get the door for me , sir ?
- Yes , Milady . - Oh , thank you , sir .
Good evening .
God , you 're beautiful .
Thank you .
Thank you for the corsage . It 's perfect .
It 's no match for you .
- Shall we go ? - Yeah .
Good Lord , what was that ?
My date .
What the hell is this ? Where 's your suit ?
It 's in the trunk .
Listen , don 't worry about it .
Look , the guys needed a ride , okay ?
Couldn 't the guys have got a ride with someone else ?
It 's better like this .
Ah-hh .
- Come on , we 're gonna party . - No .
Look , this whole thing was your idea , right ?
Anyway , you look terrific .
Hi .
This is Seymour .
We 've met .
Whoo-hoo .
- Hey , I 'm Slick . - So I noticed .
A token , nothing more .
I 'm sorry we missed your grand entrance , Kim ,
but Vi 's been very upset .
I took her for a walk to calm her down .
She 's probably just nervous .
Yeah , I hope so .
- Come on , Daddy , relax . - Oh , I 'm relaxed .
Principal by day , disco king by night .
Thanks for the dance .
- Do you believe her ? - Let 's show her what we can do .
McBride , anything ?
No , still nothing , Lieutenant .
I 'll check in later .
I thought she 'd explode .
- It that dress , it wouldn 't take much . - She looks great .
Listen , if you need a ride home afterwards .
Thanks .
- Hi . - How are you , okay ?
It 'll be okay as long as we stay on the dance floor .
- It 's tough in the trenches . - We 'll be around if you need support .
Or an extra pair of hands .
Ready ? We don 't want to keep Preppie waiting .
He 'll never miss me . He 's seen Wendy .
It 's really no big deal , Kelly . It 's like getting a shot .
Listen to the instant expert . One date , and she 's a sex counselor .
I know what I like .
No , I can 't , Drew .
Kelly , I want you so bad .
You know how I feel about you .
No .
What are you , some fairytale princess ?
Drew , please .
" Drew , please . "
If you don 't ...
I know plenty who will .
Drew , you bastard !
You 'll be back .
Now , Kelly .
Now .
Kim !
I believe this is our dance , Monty ?
We 've had every man looking for some sign of him
or that car all day .
Damn right I 'm upset ,
and I need some results , and soon , okay ?
Oh , oh .
- You okay ? - Mm-hm .
- Oh , shit . - What ?
My glasses .
You going somewhere ?
Nature calls .
Don 't go away .
Was it , uh ...
- was it okay ? - Oh , God .
Yeah , ha , me too . The best .
- Ever ? - Well ...
You 're my first too .
Really ?
Wow , there 's a million stars out there .
Yeah , I figured that 's what they were .
Can 't see a thing without my glasses .
Oh , yeah ? Well , why don 't we take a walk along the bluffs ?
Very funny .
Why don 't we do it on the bluffs ?
On the bluffs ?
Come on , it 'll be fantastic .
Wow !
Ah , I can 't see .
What was what ?
Somebody 's out there .
Why don 't , uh , why don 't we go back in the van ?
Why ?
I think I need another joint .
I think you do too .
Follow me .
I 'll just fold this up .
I can hardly believe it .
This morning , I didn 't even know you .
And I figured I was out of luck
as far as going to the prom was concerned .
And now ...
Yeah , me too .
Funny how fast our life changes .
Hand me the history book .
You think this is the time to study ?
You know , I 'll remember this night
for the rest of my life .
Of course .
So will I.
No !
Now ! Now !
Argh !
I wonder what they 're scheming now .
We 've got to show ' em who 's boss .
Look , I thought I told you I didn 't want anyone hurt .
Stop telling me what to do .
Jerk .
Hey , have you got any mascara ?
Have you got any mascara ?
Shit .
What are you doing ?
- Lou ? - Now !
Help !
Oh-hh !
Now !
Now ! Now !
I had to tell you myself . We got him .
Where ? When ?
Well , actually the state patrol got him , out near Alderson .
That 's over 50 miles from here .
Yeah , he must have left town after he killed that girl in the convent .
Well , I can start enjoying the prom .
See you in the morning , Sayer .
Good night , Lieutenant .
Hey , Drew . Have you seen my Dad ?
- Kim , where 's your father ? - I was just looking for him .
It 's almost time for the Royal Procession .
Who 's to present the bouquet ?
- Mr. Weller ? - Oh , no .
Of course , Monty . Why didn 't I think of that my ...
Loose ... there 's a killer loose . There 's a killer loose .
Poor guy 's had too much to drink .
I 'm calling for the patrol car to take him in .
We 'll be right back , Nicky . Come on , let 's go .
- What did he do ? - Just drank too much , I guess .
Hm , fits right in with this crowd .
All right , everybody , the excitement 's over .
It 's time to get ready for the Procession .
Break a leg , Your Majesty .
Oh , thank you , Maid of Honor .
Are you all set , Davy ? Well , let 's go .
It 's time .
- What about Wendy ? - Screw her .
I 'll just have sweet Kim all to myself .
So if Wendy don 't get here , we let the Hammond girl go ?
You got it .
Any questions ?
No , Buddy 'll take care of Kim .
Take off .
Okay , it 's parade time .
Hold still .
- Real cute . - You look fine .
Now don 't forget to start on the trumpets .
Now !
Don 't panic ! Don 't panic !
Nick ?
- My leg . - Come on , get up .
Come on , get up !
Now , it 's my turn .
No !
This is the police .
- Killers are coming . - Please calm down .
Other police units are on their way .
Kill !
Please calm down . Move to one side
so they can get through when they arrive . I repeat ...
Killers are coming !
Officer : Everything is under control .
Kill ! Killers are coming .
- Watch out , Kelly . - I hear you !
Oh , my God !
- Hey Nick . - There 's Jude .
Here , killer 's here .
Kill !
- Kill ! - Don 't shoot him !
- Kill ! - Kim , get back .
Halt , or I 'll shoot . What are you doing ?
Kill , kill , kill !
Kill !
I ...
I ... saw it . Saw it all .
They ... they killed her .
They ... killed her .
Robin , Robin .